{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "Cartoons",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In the “Road Runner and Coyote” cartoons, what famous sound does the Road Runner make?",
            "correct_answer": "Beep! Beep!",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Ping! Ping!",
                "Aooga! Aooga!",
                "Vroom! Vroom!"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Where should choking victims place their hands to indicate to others that they need help?",
            "correct_answer": "Around the throat",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Over the eyes",
                "On the knees",
                "On the hips"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Music",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which of these dance names is used to describe a fashionable dot?",
            "correct_answer": "Polka",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Hora",
                "Swing",
                "Lambada"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In what “language” would you say “ello-hay” to greet your friends?",
            "correct_answer": "Pig Latin",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Bull Latin",
                "Dog Latin",
                "Duck Latin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Animals",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What part of a chicken is commonly called the “drumstick?”",
            "correct_answer": "Leg",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Breast",
                "Wing",
                "Gizzard"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "What is the only position on a football team that can be “sacked?”",
            "correct_answer": "Quarterback",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Center",
                "Wide receiver",
                "Tight end"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Mythology",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "What god of love is often depicted as a chubby winged infant with a bow and arrow?",
            "correct_answer": "Cupid",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Zeus",
                "Mercury",
                "Poseidon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "What Steven Spielberg film climaxes at a place called Devil’s Tower?",
            "correct_answer": "Close Encounters of the Third Kind",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial",
                "Jurassic Park",
                "Raiders of the Lost Ark"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In what U.S. town did the famous 1881 shootout at the O.K. Corral take place?",
            "correct_answer": "Tombstone",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Laramie",
                "El Paso",
                "Dodge City"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Which of the following months has no U.S. federal holiday?",
            "correct_answer": "August",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "February",
                "September",
                "November"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Mythology",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "What mythological beast is reborn from its own ashes?",
            "correct_answer": "Phoenix",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Minotaur",
                "Dragon",
                "Golem"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science & Nature",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Who developed the first effective vaccine against polio?",
            "correct_answer": "Jonas Salk",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Albert Sabin",
                "Niels Bohr",
                "Louis Pasteur"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Which of the following is not a monotheistic religion?",
            "correct_answer": "Hinduism",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Islam",
                "Judaism",
                "Christianity"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "What architect designed the glass pyramid in the courtyard of the Louvre?",
            "correct_answer": "I.M. Pei",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Philip Johnson",
                "Le Corbusier",
                "Frank Gehry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Television",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Which of these U.S. Presidents appeared on the television series “Laugh-In”?",
            "correct_answer": "Richard Nixon",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Lyndon Johnson",
                "Jimmy Carter",
                "Gerald Ford"
            ]
        }
    ]
}
